<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Novel Scholar</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>
    <!--
    This string is used for square devices and overridden by hello_world in
    values-round/strings.xml for round devices.
    -->
    <string name="hello_world">Hello Square World!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main3"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_main4">MainActivity4</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main5">MainActivity5</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main6">MainActivity6</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search_meaning">SearchMeaning</string>
    <string name="text">Going by a range of names, including “Product Tour” and “Tutorial”, you’ve definitely
        seen these in 95% of the apps you have downloaded. Right after the splash screen,
        you’ll be presented with a screen which tell you
        how to navigate to the reading section."\n"You have probably heard advice like "create a hook"
         and "grab the reader attention." But what kind of
        stuff actually grabs someone attention? It is human nature to want to think about an answer
        to a question we are asked, and since it is presupposed that our article already has the answer to
        the question you asked in the introduction.I can think of a lot of things, actually, but they probably
        wouldn’t be appropriate for an introduction."\n\n"
        Novel Scholar is an offline application with multiple different sections that would help the reader in caching of the important notes , check pronounciation and many
more .Novel read is one of the application that not only helps the reader in building a strong base but also help you to dive through various others learnig path.
The app is build keeping in mind the readers interest in reading novels. The app consist of novels of high star rating .
        It included best novels of each and every category . Many premium novels that are not available free of cost will also be present in this app .The app is
layered in multiple sections with each section convey some important functions .Apart from just reading novels , the novel important content can also be saved
in the app memory . The data stored in the application will not occupy any physical memory of the device .This app is remarkably good as it contains  various
sections that will help the learner in proper understanding of the novel .Any important sentence or phrase can be properly save permanently .After installing
the app , it will not consume much memory of your mobile phone .All the app features are impeccable and provide scintillating performance .It is user friendly ,
easy to install and productive in function . All the novel lover would enjoy using this app ."\n\n"
        Key Features :"\n"
"\n""You do not have to strain your eyes going through the app as the novels included are compact in size ,customizable font size and theme color .
"\n"Every important phrases of novels can be save in app memory without any need to memorize them .
"\n"You can check the pronounciation of words which are not easy to spell.
"\n"App consist of multiple sections . You can easily navigate through different section .
"\n"The memory occupancy of the app is too less .Even the phone with low memory capacity and RAM can support the app with all ease .
I recommend every novel lover to install this app today and curve your future for tomorrow. It is beneficiary ,free of cost and a time saviour choice for the
youths . So, please install this application."\n"
        The app consist of various section where apart from just reading  you can preserve your important content
    in the note section of the app which will be stored permanently untill  you do not remove it.This section will not
    occupy the physical memory of your device.The reading section consist of novels of high star rating. Reading these novels will surely boost
        readers learning skills.In this app, we have included both fiction and non fiction apps those are written by famous writers.
        The novels are full of thriller ,action , romance and comedy ."\n\n"We have not included any content
    that are unsolicited or outrage the reader The app is not the part of any copywright infringement
    All the sections are self made and patent published. Every category of novels are included keeping in
    mind the readers interest.Reading these novels helps you to improve your english to a great extent .</string>
</resources>